GOETZ



CONTACT

Snoveien 10, 1363 Høvik

P +47 912 66 500

anna.gtz087@outlook.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ anna-goetz-29294b199/

https://annagtz2022.github.io/ portfolio_AKJ/

EDUCATION

Master's in Economics of enterprise, 2015

Odessa National Polytechnic University, Ukraine

Bachelor's in Metallurgy, 2012

National Metallurgical Academy of Ukraine

SKILLS

- · Research and analysis
- · Critical thinking
- · Continuous learning
- Efficient work practices
- · Meticulous attention to detail
- Fast-paced work environment
- Advanced in Excel (incl. Power Pivot), PowerPoint
- Familiar with SQL, Power BI, and Python
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills

LANGUAGES

English fluent Ukrainian native Russian native

HOBBIES













Fund & Portfolio Analyst

ABOUT ME

I am a versatile professional with a diverse skill set and extensive experience in various areas, including financial product sales, management, research, data analysis, and visualization. My proactive approach, enthusiasm, rapid learning ability, and adeptness in navigating high-pressure environments have consistently contributed to exceeding targets, leading to frequent promotions and increased responsibilities. I possess exceptional communication skills and have honed my ability to build trusted relationships with people from various backgrounds.

EXPERIENCE

Embassy of Ukraine in the Kingdom of Norway | 2022-2023 **Humanitarian Operations Assistant, Volunteer**

I prepared shipping documents, tracked aid donations and shipments in spreadsheets, and calculated the value of humanitarian aid.

Infosystem Center LLC | Odessa, Ukraine | 2019
Information and communication network operator

I assisted users with software functionality and effectively addressed claims between clients and drivers, providing comprehensive support and resolving any issues that arose.

PLASKE PJSC (cargo company) | Odessa, Ukraine | 2017-2018 **Accountant**

I accurately recorded and oversaw financial transactions, collaborating with cross-functional teams to ensure the timely and accurate delivery of relevant data for daily operational evaluations. Additionally, I effectively managed payment accounts and maintained financial balance between systems.

PLASKE PJSC (cargo company) | Odessa, Ukraine | 2015-2017 Office Support Specialist

I was responsible for end-to-end order handling, support process optimization, handling service contracts (including supplier research, evaluation and selection), budget planning, invoice processing, office supply and equipment management, and its inventory audits. Through meticulous research and comprehensive data analysis of office expenses and processes, I successfully identified valuable cost-saving opportunities and improved process efficiency. Additionally, I maintained open lines of communication with vendors and stakeholders to ensure smooth operations, and promptly resolving issues.

Consumer Center LLC (loan center) | Odessa, Ukraine | 2014-2015 **Department manager**

Managing customer accounts, and training and supervising new employees to provide high-quality service have helped me consistently exceed sales revenue targets. Additionally, I maintained office policies and procedures, managed equipment inventory, and ensured efficient office operations. I also maintained accurate records of all funds and was primarily responsible for their collection.

Delta Bank JSC | Yalta, Crimea, Ukraine | 2011-2014

Account manager

I efficiently manage clients' accounts, providing them with financial advice and effective solutions, while also processing transactions with utmost accuracy. I have consistently demonstrated a strong ability to build and foster enduring client relationships, leading to their continued loyalty and satisfaction. This ability have helped me surpassing sales revenue targets, and have resulted in my achievement of being one of the top three performers among bank branches.